A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller photographs, Room 5600, Rockefeller family office, Series 2 FA455
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Nelson A. Rockefeller Photographs, Room 5600, Rockefeller family office, 1920-1979; 2; 32.73 Cubic Feet
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Photographs, 1909-1979; 18.33 Cubic Feet 39 legal document boxes.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portraits
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - HEW picture - Singer, 1954; (5) (Box 28, Folder 429)
        {1008.4/56 through 1008.4/60}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Gallagher, 1958; (2); {1008.15/363 through 1008.15/364} (Box 28, Folder 430)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - World Wide Photos, 1958 July; (2) (Box 28, Folder 431)
        {1008.15/382 through 1008.15/383}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Gabor Eder, 1958; (17); {1008.15/365 through 1008.15/381} (Box 28, Folder 432)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Holding Glasses in Some Views, 1958; (2) (Box 29, Folder 433)
        {1008.15/384 through 1008.15/385}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Official Gubernatorial Photograph, Gallagher, 1959; (4) (Box 29, Folder 434)
        {1008.15/386 through 1008.15/389}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait by NYS Department of Commerce, 1959; (4) (Box 29, Folder 435)
        {1008.15/546 through 1008.15/557}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Official Photo, 1959 February; (1) (Box 29, Folder 436)
        {1008.15/390}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Official Photo, Arthur Daly, 1961; (1) (Box 29, Folder 437)
        {1008.15/391}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - 1964 Official Campaign Photo, Halsman, (15) (Box 29, Folder 438)
        {1008.15/392 through 1008.15/406}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait by Olson Photo, 1960; (3) (Box 29, Folder 439)
        {1008.15/204; 1008.15/229; 1008.15/230}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - James J. Kriegsmann, circa 1960; (1) (Box 29, Folder 440)
        {1008.15/407}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait for Life Magazine, 1968; (1) (Box 29, Folder 441)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Halsmann, circa 1970; (1) (Box 29, Folder 442)
        {1008.15/408}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Campaign Photo Negatives, 1964 (some with Mrs Nelson A. Rockefeller), (1 photo, 7 negatives) (Box 29, Folder 443)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - 1964 Campaign Photos (Mounted), (3) (Box 29, Folder 444)
        {1008.15/419 through 1008.15/421}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait - Vice President, (2) (Box 30, Folder 445)
        {1008.26/1 through 1008.26/2}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, circa 1958; (1) (Box 30, Folder 446)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait, c.1975 (Box 30, Folder 447)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portrait, c. 1978; (1) (Box 30, Folder 448)
        {1008.26/14}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Oversized Portraits, (photocopies) (Box 30, Folder 449)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portraits, (photocopies) (Box 30, Folder 450)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portraits - Informal
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Campaign Pictures, 1958; (18) (Box 30, Folder 451)
        {1008.15/422 through 1008.15/439}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Informal Portraits, Gubernatorial, c. 1959; (1) (Box 30, Folder 452)
        {1008.15/3605}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Informal Portraits, Gubernatorial, c.1960; (1) (Box 30, Folder 453)
        {1008.15/3600}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Informal Portraits, Gubernatorial, c. 1961; (3) (Box 30, Folder 454)
        {1008.15/3601 - 1008.15/3603}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Informal Portraits, Gubernatorial, c. 1965; (6) (Box 30, Folder 455)
        {1008.15/440 through 1008.15/445}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Broadcasting on Mexican Radio, 1945; (1) (Box 30, Folder 456)
        {1008.4/61}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller at microphone - WLW, 1945; (1) {1008.4/62} (Box 30, Folder 457)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Informal, 1967; (1) (Box 30, Folder 458)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Informal, 1969 May; (1) (Box 30, Folder 459)
        {1008.15/3612}
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Informal - Vice Presidential Portraits, 1974-1975; (10) (Box 30, Folder 460)
        {1008.26/4 through 1008.26/13}
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Travel - Latin America
      - CIAA (Box 31, Folder 461)
      - General, 1937-1950; (39) (Box 31, Folder 462)
      - Negatives, #10 through # 80, (52 negatives) (Box 31, Folder 463)
        [missing #s 10, 12, 15, 21, 22, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 37, 44, 49]
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Trip to Mexico, 1943; (13) [73] [68] [45] (Box 31, Folder 464)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Marion Anderson, Delores Del Rio, Mexico, 1943; (9) (Box 31, Folder 465)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Trip to Brazil, 1956; (7) [23] [34] [36] [38] [42] [43] (Box 31, Folder 466)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Trip to Brazil, 1958; (8) [48] [50] [51] [53] [55] [56] [57] [59] (Box 31, Folder 467)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Travel- Post Election Trips (Brazil, Venezuela, Rio de Janeiro), 1958 November 18-21 (Box 32, Folder 468)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, (Brazil), 1959; (3) (Box 32, Folder 469)
        {1008.15/446 through 1008.15/448}
      - International Basic Economic Corporation (IBEC) - Nelson A. Rockefeller with IBEC Staff on Visit to Brazil, 1947-1958 (Box 32, Folder 470)
      - untitled, (9 slides, 42 photos, 2 contact sheets with 20 images) (Box 32, Folder 471)
      - Presidential Mission to Latin America, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 472)
      - Presidential Mission to Latin America, 1969; (4) (Box 32, Folder 473)
      - Nicaragua (Album), 1969 (Box 32, Folder 474)
      - Guyana (Album), 1969 (Box 32, Folder 475)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Travel - Other, 1956-1976
      - Travel - Unidentified Trips, (15) (Box 32, Folder 476)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Liberia, 1956; (4) (Box 32, Folder 477)
      - Texas, 1952 (Box 32, Folder 478)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Nigeria Trip, R. Fleming, Nigerian Government Representatives, 1960 October; (35) (Box 32, Folder 479)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller and Mary C. Rockefeller on Nigerian Trip, 1960 October; (35) (Box 32, Folder 480)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller and MFR at Berlin Wall, 1963 September 29; (6) (Box 33, Folder 481)
      - Germany, Viewpoint Magazine, 1963; (4) (Box 33, Folder 482)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Trips - Dorado Beach, Puerto Rico, 1966; (4) (Box 33, Folder 483)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Trip to Portugal, 1968; (7) (Box 33, Folder 484)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Trip to Barbados, 1969; (9) (Box 33, Folder 485)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Trip to Israel, 1972; (91) (Box 33, Folder 486)
      - Dorado Beach, Puerto Rico, 1974; (8) (Box 33, Folder 487)
      - Vice-Presidential Bicentennial Tour (Box 33)
        - Saudi Arabia, 1975 March 25-27; (44) (Box 33, Folder 488)
        - Egypt, 1975 October; (3) (Box 33, Folder 489)
        - Spain, 1975 November 23-27; (9) (Box 33, Folder 490)
        - Tunisia, 1976 March 20; (4) (Box 33, Folder 491)
        - Paris, France, 1976 March 21-23; (19) (Box 33, Folder 492)
        - Malaysia, 1976 March 26-28; (23) (Box 33, Folder 493)
        - Italy, Earthquake, 1976 May 13; (11) (Box 33, Folder 494)
        - Frankfurt, Berlin, 1976 May 13-15; (31) (Box 33, Folder 495)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller and MFR in India, 1978 May 3; (1) {1008.15/3614} (Box 33, Folder 496)
    - Group Portraits-Family (Box 34, Folder 497)
    - Homes - Executive Mansion - Fire, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 498)
    - Margaretta Murphy Rockefeller (MFR) (Happy) (Box 34, Folder 499)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Art - Executive Mansion, 1961 (Box 34, Folder 500)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Business
      - IBEC - LSR and WR with Marin Munoz, 1955 (Box 34, Folder 501)
      - IBEC - Puerto Rican Supermarket and Housing Developments, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 502)
      - Rockefeller Center - Time Life Building, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 503)
      - Rockefeller Center - Time Life Building, 1958 (Box 34, Folder 504)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Candids - Rockefeller Center, 1950 (Box 34, Folder 505)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Government Service
      - Gubernatorial Campaigns - Rodman and Michael (Box 34, Folder 506)
      - Gubernatorial Offices - Empire State Plaza - Art Collection (Box 34, Folder 507)
      - Gubernatorial Offices - Saratoga Performing Arts Center, 1966 (Box 34, Folder 508)
      - Under Secretary of Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1946 (Box 34, Folder 509)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Philanthropies - MOMA (Box 34, Folder 510)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Portraits - Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 511)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Travel - Honeymoon - Egypt (Box 35, Folder 512)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Travel - Honeymoon - Egypt (Box 35, Folder 513)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Travel - Honeymoon - Egypt (Box 35, Folder 514)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Travel - Honeymoon - Egypt (Box 35, Folder 515)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Travel - Honeymoon - Egypt (Box 35, Folder 516)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Travel - Honeymoon - Egypt (Box 35, Folder 517)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Travel - Honeymoon - Egypt (Box 35, Folder 518)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Travel - Honeymoon - Egypt (Box 35, Folder 519)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Travel - Honeymoon - Egypt (Box 35, Folder 520)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Travel - Honeymoon - Egypt (Box 35, Folder 521)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Travel - Honeymoon - Egypt (Box 35, Folder 522)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Travel - Honeymoon - Egypt (Box 35, Folder 523)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Travel - Honeymoon - Egypt - Post Cards (Box 35, Folder 524)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Travel - Honeymoon - Egypt - Post Cards (Box 35, Folder 525)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Travel - Honeymoon - Egypt - Post Cards (Box 35, Folder 526)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Miscellaneous
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller on the Hindenburg, 1936 October 9 (Box 36, Folder 527)
        Nelson Rockefeller aboard the Hindenburg on October 9, 1936. This event was described as an exhibition flight arranged by Esso marketers and Standard Oil Company of New Jersey. Banker Winthrop Aldrich accompanied Rockefeller. Aldrich was the brother of Rockefeller's mother. General Frederich von Boetticher also was aboard.
      - Mococa Brazil (Box 36, Folder 528)
      - New York City 30th National Foreign Trade Convention, October 27 (Box 36, Folder 529)
      - Monastery Koya-San (Box 36, Folder 530)
      - Kykuit Party (Box 36, Folder 531)
      - Temple Nara (Box 36, Folder 532)
      - Groundbreaking at Eisenhower College Seneca Falls NY (Box 36, Folder 533)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Eleanor Roosevelt, 1942 January 9 (Box 36, Folder 534)
      - Ritz Carlton Latin American Fair Preview, 1942 January 16 (Box 36, Folder 535)
      - Inter American Commission of Women, 1944 April (Box 36, Folder 536)
      - Tiatilco, Mexico, 1947 December 14 (Box 36, Folder 537)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller with former Heads of World Bank (Box 36, Folder 538)
      - Puerto Rico Governors Conference, 1959 August (Box 36, Folder 539)
      - Spain, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 540)
      - Fashion Institute of Technology scholarship Dinner, 1965 June (Box 36, Folder 541)
      - United Nations, 1965 October 25 (Box 36, Folder 542)
      - Pierre Hotel HRH Prince Philip, 1966 March 18 (Box 36, Folder 543)
      - Carlyle Hotel Nelson A. Rockefeller and Indira Gandhi, 1966 March 31 (Box 36, Folder 544)
      - Greek Independence Day Parade, 1966 May 15 (Box 36, Folder 545)
      - Buffalo NY and Labor Leaders, 1966 October 19 (Box 36, Folder 546)
      - Washington DC Republican Coordinating Committee Meeting, 1967 December 12 (Box 36, Folder 547)
      - 1967 (Box 36, Folder 548)
      - Capitol Swearing In, 1967 January (Box 36, Folder 549)
      - NY City Brotherhood in Action Dinner, 1967 May 10 (Box 36, Folder 550)
      - New York City Catholic Interracial Council of NY, 1967 May 23 (Box 36, Folder 551)
      - National Institute of Social Science Photographs, 1967 November 28 (Box 36, Folder 552)
      - Nixon Inauguration, 1969 January (Box 36)
      - New York City Swearing In, 1970 December 31 (Box 36, Folder 554)
      - Republican Governors' Conference, 1973 May (Box 36, Folder 555)
      - Man of Conscience Award, 1973 December 11 (Box 36, Folder 556)
      - Franklin Delano Roosevelt Four Freedoms Foundation Award to Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1974 (Box 36, Folder 557)
      - Family Christmas Party, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 558)
      - Rockefeller Center Miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 559)
      - Koya-San (Box 37, Folder 560)
      - Koya-San (Box 37, Folder 561)
      - Temples Koya-San (Box 37, Folder 562)
      - Cemetery Koya-San (Box 37, Folder 563)
      - Tokyo Shrine (Box 37, Folder 564)
      - Tokyo Museum of Folk Art (Box 37, Folder 565)
      - Gardens Kyoto (Box 37, Folder 566)
      - Garden Kyoto (Box 37, Folder 567)
      - Nara (Box 37, Folder 568)
      - Nara Horyhiji Temple (Box 37, Folder 569)
      - From train, going to Nikko (Box 37, Folder 570)
      - Nikko (Box 37, Folder 571)
      - Japan Golf (Box 37, Folder 572)
      - Japan Fishing (Box 37, Folder 573)
      - Invitations (Box 37, Folder 574)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller wins election (Box 37, Folder 575)
      - Candids (Box 37, Folder 576)
      - Happy Rockefeller (MFR) (Box 37, Folder 577)
      - Western (U.S.) Hunting Trip (Box 37, Folder 578)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller with dignitaries (negatives) (Box 38, Folder 579)
        - Negatives (Box 38, Folder 579)
          - Nelson A. Rockefeller and Messer Smith, 1942
          - IAC - Nelson A. Rockefeller at airport
          - Gen Andrews, Amb Wilson Panama Signal Core
          - D-0448 - Nelson A. Rockefeller, J. Rovensky, National Defense Advisory Comm
          - Reed, Grew, Clayton, McLeisch, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Dunn Aeme
          - Nelson A. Rockefeller christening plane
          - Other Business Show Impact of Festival Visitors
          - Unidentified
      - Happy Rockefeller (MFR) Golfing (Box 38, Folder 580)
      - Candids - NAR, Happy Rockefeller (MFR) and others (Box 38, Folder 581)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Unidentified, (9 folders) (Box 38, Folder 582)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Happy Rockefeller (MFR) Unidentified (Box 38, Folder 583)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Unidentified (Box 38, Folder 584)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Happy Rockefeller (MFR) Unidentified (Box 38, Folder 585)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Unidentified (Box 38, Folder 586)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Unidentified (Box 38, Folder 587)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Happy Rockefeller (MFR) Unidentified (Box 38, Folder 588)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, Happy Rockefeller (MFR) Unidentified (Box 38, Folder 589)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller and family Unidentified (Box 38, Folder 590)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller, MFR and Children, Kykuit, 1963 October; (box of slides) (Box 38)
      - Nancy Sirkis Magnum Photos - Nelson A. Rockefeller and Happy sailing, (box of slides) (Box 38)
  - Nelson A. Rockefeller Oversized, 1920-1977; 14.4 Cubic Feet 12 oversized boxes.
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Oversized Photographs
      - Art (Box O 1)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Homes, Seal Harbor, Maine
        - House at Seal Harbor, Maine (Box O 2)
        - Color Photos of Gardens and Grounds (Box O 2)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Family - Portraits, 1931-1965
        - Portraits of Nelson A. Rockefeller and MFR by Halsman, circa 1965; (9 copies) (Box O 2)
        - Portraits of Nelson A. Rockefeller's Children by Delar, circa 1940; (3 poses) (Box O 2)
        - Bridal Portrait of Mary C. Rockefeller by Bachrach, 1931; (3 copies) (Box O 2)
        - Portrait of John D. Rockefeller Sr., John D. Rockefeller Jr., Nelson A. Rockefeller and Rodman C. Rockefeller, circa 1933 (Box O 2)
        - Portrait of Abby A. Rockefeller with Grandson Rodman C. Rockefeller, circa 1935 (Box O 2)
        - Group Portraits of Nelson A. Rockefeller, Mary C. Rockefeller, LSR, Abby Rockefeller Milton, Mr. and Mrs. John D. Rockefeller Jr., John D. Rockefeller, Sr., and Grandchildren, circa 1935; (2 poses) (Box O 2)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Son Rodman, circa 1935; (2 copies) (Box O 2)
      - Politics, 1966-1968
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Photos, Miscellaneous, 1966-1968; (7 photos) (Box O 3)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Portraits, 1930-1948
        - Portrait by Garrett, circa 1945; (2 copies) (Box O 3)
        - Portraits by Koshiba, circa 1930; (10 copies) (Box O 3)
        - Portraits by Newman, circa 1948; (4 copies) (Box O 3)
        - Portraits by Delar, circa 1935; (3 copies) (Box O 3)
        - Portrait by Harris and Ewing, circa 1945; (2 boxes, 13 copies) (Box O 4)
        - Portrait by Karsh, circa 1945; (2 boxes, 30 copies) (Box O 4)
        - Portrait by Halsman, circa 1965; (6 copies) (Box O 4)
      - Colleges and Universities, 1965-1974
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller at Columbia University Commencement, circa 1965 (Box O 4)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller at Dartmouth Reunion, 1974 June 18 (Box O 4)
      - Dignitaries and Friends, 1942-1977
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with President Roosevelt, 1942 (Box O 4)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with President Truman, 1949 (Box O 4)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with President Eisenhower, 1954 (Box O 4)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with President Ford, 1977 (Box O 4)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with John F. Kennedy (Box O 4)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with President Segni of Italy, 1964 (Box O 4)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with President Betancourt of Venezuela, 1963 (Box O 4)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Adlai Stevenson (Box O 4)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Ben Gurion (Box O 4)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Robert Wagner (Box O 4)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Brazilian Officials (Box O 4)
        - Portraits of Various Dignitaries and Friends (Box O 4)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Robert Wagner and Walter O'Malley at Gracie mansion, 1957 September (Box O 4)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Chancellor Erdhart (Box O 4)
        - Unidentified (Box O 4)
      - Homes
        - "Sea Star" Photos and Slides (Box O 4)
        - Interior Photos (Box O 4)
        - Monte Sacro Ranch (Box O 4)
        - House at Seal Harbor, Maine: Gardens (Box O 4)
        - Admiral's House, Washington, DC (Box O 4)
        - Kykuit's West Porch - Taken by Nelson (Box O 4)
      - Political, 1964
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller Campaigning: Oregon Primary, 1964 (Box O 5)
        - California Primary, 1964 (Box O 5)
        - Fall 1975 Smithsonian Regents Meeting, 1975 Fall (Box O 5)
        - White House Lyndon B. Johnson, 1966 March 12 (Box O 5)
        - Gubernatorial (Box O 5)
        - Unidentified Campaigning (Box O 5)
        - Time & Life Building - Groundbreaking, dedication, Interior & Exterior Shots, 1962-1963 (Box O 5)
      - Portraits - Informal, 1935-1975
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller Photo, circa 1930 (Box O 5)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Top Hat, circa 1935 (Box O 5)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller Playing Golf, circa 1935 (Box O 5)
        - Special Assistant Photo, 1955 (Box O 5)
        - Portrait, circa 1958 (Box O 5)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller at Podium (Box O 5)
        - Vice-Presidential Photo, circa 1975 (Box O 5)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Family - Portraits, 1958-1969
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller Children, Portraits (Box O 5)
        - Margaretta F. Rockefeller (MFR) (Happy) Portrait, 1969 (Box O 5)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with Brothers, c. 1955; (1 copy) (Box O 5)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller and Sons Sailing in Maine, c. 1958 (Box O 5)
        - LOOK Magazine Photos of Family, Farm, and Politics, c. 1958 or 1960 (Box O 5)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller and Mary C. Rockefeller at Monte Sacro, circa 1961 (Box O 5)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with brothers and sister at the Eyrie, circa 1955 (Box O 5)
      - Travel, 1958-1976 (Box O 5)
        - Trip to Brazil, 1958 November (Box O 5)
        - Presidential Mission to Latin America, 1969 (Box O 5)
        - Trip to Germany: Berlin and Frankfurt, 1976 May (Box O 5)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller with bear (Box O 5)
        - Newspaper Articles (photocopies) (Box O 5)
        - Unidentified Rolled Campaign Photos, (2) (Box O 5)
      - Portraits - Formal, 1931-1974
        - Portrait, 1931; (2 copies) (Box O 6)
        - Portrait by Karsh, circa 1945; (multiple copies) (Box O 6)
        - Portraits by Harris and Ewing, circa 1945 (Box O 6)
        - Portrait - Wendell Mac Rae, circa 1945; (1 copy) (Box O 7)
        - Office Portraits, circa 1950; (3 copies) (Box O 7)
        - Portrait, 1959; (4 copies) (Box O 7)
        - Portrait by Eder, 1958; (5 copies) (Box O 7)
        - Gubernatorial Portrait, 1959 January; (12 copies) (Box O 7)
        - Portrait by Halsman, 1964; (12 copies) (Box O 7)
        - Portrait by Halsman, 1965 (Box O 7)
        - Portrait - James J. Kriegsmann, 1964; (1 copy) (Box O 7)
        - Portrait - Life Photos by Eliot Eliston, 1965; (2 copies) (Box O 7)
        - Vice-Presidential Portraits, 1974; (19 copies) (Box O 7)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Albums
      - Gubernatorial, 1959-1968
        - Swearing-In of Jacob Grumet as New York State Supreme Court Justice (Blue), 1968 (Box O 8)
        - National Governors' Conference, Lake Tahoe, Nevada, 1973 (Box O 8)
        - Spring Republican Governors' Conference, New York, NY, 1973 (Box O 8)
        - Republican Governors' Association Spring Conference, New York, NY, 1973 May 9-12 (Box O 8)
      - Personal, 1920-1963 (Box O 9)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller and Margaretta Murphy Rockefeller: Honeymoon at Monte Sacro (red Life Magazine album), 1963 May (Box O 9)
      - Travel, 1968-1969 (Box O 9)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller Visit to Calouste Gulbenkian Foundation, Lisbon, Portugal, (green), 1968 November (Box O 9)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller Trip to Guatemala, post card views, 1944 (Box O 9)
        - National museum of Siam (probably from world tour honeymoon trip, 1930-1931), circa 1930-1931 (Box O 9)
      - Venezuela, 1962-1976 (Box O 9)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller Farms, Inc. 1962 (brown) (Box O 9)
        - Nelson A. Rockefeller Farms, Inc. 1976 (white and blue) (Box O 9)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller Albums - Personal - Family Scrapbooks (Box O 10)
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller - Childhood Album (Box O 12)
      - Monte Sacro Album, 1971 (Box O 12)
    - Nelson A. Rockefeller Slides
      - Slides, 1957-1969
        - Trip to Isfahan, Iran (slides by Nelson A. Rockefeller), 1957 April (Box O 10)
        - World Series (Slides by Nelson A. Rockefeller), 1969 (Box O 10)
        - Vacation in Utah (slides by Nelson A. Rockefeller) (Box O 10)
        - Governor's Mansion in Albany, undated (Box O 10)
        - Trip to Spain, 1964 November (Box O 10)
    - Rolled Photographs
      - Nelson A. Rockefeller waving in car (Box O 10)
      - Homes, 1 panoramic, 1 blueprint, 1 aerial (all rolled). (Box O 11)